tecake.in 2017-03-12

# Privacy Policy

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to comment on the article, entering a contest, or ordering e-mail newsletters.

If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on the website, but you will not be able to comment and subscribe daily newsletter or areas that require your personal details.

#### How is information collected?

**From Cookies**. Like many websites, we use “cookies.” We use persistent, identifying cookies to detect your browser, remember your information and to link your activities to you. While you can take steps to warn off, block or disable cookies, if you do, the site may not function and appear as we have designed it. For more information about cookies, including controlling and deleting them, please visit the [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) website.

**From traffic references.**  when you visit a website, you unveil certain information about you, such as your IP address, time of visit, place from which you accessed our website. [www.tecake.com](http://www.tecake.com/), like other operators, stores this information.

**From Social Networks.  **While entering a contest, or ordering e-mail newsletters, we may ask to share website content on your Social Networks like Facebook, Twitter etc. So you should review your privacy settings on your social network accounts because those settings determine and govern what information may be made available to us.

#### Security

The TeCake strictly protects the security of your personal information and honours your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

#### Distribution

The TeCake does not distribute personal information to any third parties without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on website, that some of your personal information is available on publicly accessible web page(s). One example would be commenting the posts.

Also, The TeCake is not responsible for the content published within the under quotes (” “) on the website, as it is copied from a source or a press release. The copyright of this content also belongs to their respective owners.

#### Changes to this document

Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. The TeCake may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.

For any suggestions and comments regarding The TeCake or our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at **_contact[at]tecake.com_**
